Okay folks, things are moving so fast.
好吧，伙计们，事情发展得太快了。
This is open claw meets 3D printing. So we got the kids a bamboo.
这是张开的爪子遇上 3D 打印。所以我们给孩子们买了一根竹子。
machine for Christmas. I mean, it's for the whole family and I use it a ton. But in spirit, it was like for the kids.
圣诞节的机器。我的意思是，它适合全家人，而且我经常使用它。但在精神上，这就像孩子们一样。
like for education for you know learning about like 3d printing so uh we've
喜欢教育，因为你知道学习 3D 打印，所以呃我们已经
so many prints but from the bamboo marketplace which has a lot of options
这么多印刷品，但来自竹子市场，有很多选择
I saw recently, though, that the new Gemini DeepThink model, I think 3, can generate STL 5.
不过，我最近看到新的 Gemini DeepThink 模型（我认为是 3）可以生成 STL 5。
So I got an API key for that and gave it to one of my open clause that I'm making more technical.
因此，我为此获得了一个 API 密钥，并将其交给了我正在使之更具技术性的开放条款之一。
Cole. So Cole, who is an open claw, I wanted him to control the machine and this print
油菜。所以科尔，他是一个张开爪子的人，我想让他控制机器和这张照片
is finally being sent to the machine by Cole instead of me, okay? So this is Cole controlling the machine.
终于被科尔而不是我送到机器了好吗？这是科尔在控制机器。
And I have Cole generating his own STL files.
我让 Cole 生成他自己的 STL 文件。
And my goal here is that Cole can then communicate with my open claw who manages my homeschool.
我的目标是科尔可以与管理我的家庭学校的我张开爪子进行交流。
curriculum and see all of the lessons I have planned for like the next week or so and choose to print
课程并查看我计划下周左右的所有课程，然后选择打印
something in the 3d world that's useful to that lesson so let's say well this week for instance
3D 世界中的一些东西对这节课很有用，所以让我们以本周为例
for science we're teaching um like the bones and muscles how muscles pull on bones and joints so
对于科学，我们正在教授嗯，就像骨骼和肌肉一样，肌肉如何拉动骨骼和关节，所以
So I'm going like, so what if, and I just need to figure out if Cole can actually generate like how good his STL files from Germany can.
所以我想，如果，我只需要弄清楚 Cole 是否真的可以生成像他来自德国的 STL 文件一样多好的文件。
gemini can be because this is more of like a simple thing but if coal can generate like an example of a
双子座可能是因为这更像是一件简单的事情，但如果煤炭可以像一个例子一样产生
like two bones connected, then he could actually print a model for the kids that I pull out.
就像连接的两根骨头一样，然后他实际上可以为我拉出来的孩子们打印一个模型。
and use for that lesson. So that's where I'm trying to go like a next level, like bringing some of these things.
并用于该课程。所以这就是我想要更上一层楼的地方，比如带来一些东西。
into the real world giving my open clause like real world clause so we'll see how it goes
进入现实世界，给出我的开放条款，就像现实世界条款一样，所以我们会看看它是如何进行的
I've proven that Cole at OpenClaw can use the machine, but can he generate brilliant files? Time will tell.
我已经证明 OpenClaw 的 Cole 可以使用这台机器，但他能生成出色的文件吗？时间会证明一切。